Sthitadhee Panthadas

I have been very keen to switch my career towards computer programming for the last two years. I believe I perform better and find more meaning here. Whenever I am solving problems or coding, I feel motivated. I am looking to, therefore, convert that motivation to provide scaled business solutions.

22/23 Sukrabad, Shapnil, Dhaka-1207, Bangladesh (880)1790478408 sthitpanth01@gmail.com https://briansteel.github.io/Portfolio/https://github.com/BrianSteel

EXPERIENCE

NAJM, Ventura Iconia, Level 3 Holding 37, Block H, Road 11, Dhaka 1213 — Content Writer

June 2020 - PRESENT

Writing on WordPress + plugins + themes, CRM and other marketing tools

Pridesys IT LTD, Garden Road, Kazi Nazrul Islam Ave, Dhaka-1205— *Intern*

JUNE 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2019

Worked under supervision targeting - C and Javascript (HTML +CSS).

Dhanmondi Tutorial, Road No: 8, Dhanmondi — Science Teacher

JULY 2013 - DECEMBER 2013

Teaching physics, chemistry, and biology + floor monitoring

EDUCATION

University of Dhaka— Bsc in Leather Product Engineering

JAN 2015 - DECEMBER 2019

CGPA - 3.82 [99th percentile] (published in December 2019)

Dhanmondi Tutorial, Dhanmondi — A level, O Levels

MAY 2001 - JANUARY 2015

A level: 2A*, 2A, 1B O level: 6A*, 2A, 1B

PROJECT

ISS Geolocation — *Geolocates International Space Station*Punching Joker — *A very simple Vue JS game*

Refer to my portfolio and GitHub account for more info. (Top right corner)



SKILLS

Photoshop, VS Code, git, vocalist, writer.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C and javascript (intermediate), C++ and python (beginner)

LANGUAGES

English (fluent) - 2020 IELTS score 8 band overall, Bangla (Fluent), German(B1), French(A2)

AWARDS

Daily star and Edexcel Award for O and A level.

Award for department topper.